gant.com 2018-07-27

# Privacy and Cookies Information for Gant Official Site

## PRIVACY

### Privacy Policy

GANT USA Corporation ("we", "us" or the "Company") collects customer information to improve our customers' shopping experience and to share with our customers, our products, services and promotions. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you when you visit our website, http://gant.com (the **"Website** "), and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information. This policy also applies to information we collect from you in e-mail or by other electronic means, such as text messages, and to information we collect through your use of mobile applications. This policy does not apply to information you send to us or that we collect through other means, such as via telephone, or through the use of the mail, and it does not apply to information collected by third parties. The Website is operated by GANT USA Corporation.

#### Website Accessibility Notice

Gant USA Corporation is committed to making the information on its website accessible to all, including  individuals with disabilities, and to ensuring its website complies with Title III of the Americans with Disabilities Act by using World Wide Web Consortium's (W3C) Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) 2.0 Level A Success Criteria.  Please keep in mind that our efforts are ongoing, therefore, there may be certain areas of our website that achieve increased accessibility at a rate different than others during a given period of time.   If you would like to report any concern or difficulty accessing information on our website, or request access to content that is currently unavailable to you, please contact our website administrator at +1 (646) 367-5416.

#### What information do we collect?

When ordering or registering on our Website, you may be asked to enter information that can individually identify you, such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and credit card information (collectively, " **Personal Information** "). We may also collect information about you which does not individually identify you, through use of various technologies (such as cookies), and other information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website (for example, your IP address), and usage details (collectively, " **Non-Personal Information** "). This information may be collected when you provide it to us, or automatically as you navigate through our Website.

#### What do we use your information for?

We collect your Personal Information to provide a service to you and process your orders, to provide you with information about our products, to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us (such as billing), to notify you of any changes to our Website and our products and services that we offer through it, and in any other way we may describe to you when you provide the information to us. We may also use your Personal Information to contact you about goods, services or promotions that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please click on the "Unsubscribe" link in the e-mails that you receive from us. If your unsubscribe request does not take effect within ten (10) business days, please e-mail us at customer-service@gant.com. Non-Personal Information is collected to allow us to improve our Website and our products, evaluate the Website traffic and transaction patterns, and to perform statistical and other evaluations of the Website's performance. Non-Personal Information that we collect also allows us to store information about your preferences (so that we may customize our Website according to your individual interests), speed up your searches, and recognize you when you return to our Website.

#### Cookies

We use cookies, as well as other technologies such as Flash and pixel tags, to recognize you and your preferences to make shopping easier and provide you with a more customized experience on our Website. Cookies are pieces of data that we automatically store on your computer if your computer accepts cookies. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information such as your name, address or any financial information on your computer. We place a unique user ID number on your cookie which allows us to access information that will improve your shopping experience, such as holding items in your shopping cart, accessing your address book, or providing you with customized pages based on your past viewing or purchasing preferences. We also use cookies to track traffic to different areas of the Website in order to make improvements and optimize your shopping experience. If you do not wish to have a cookie on your system, you can set your browser preferences to refuse them. In order to disable cookies, please consult your browser's help section for instructions.

#### Who do we share your information with?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personal Information, except as set forth in this policy. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties are bound by confidentiality requirements. We may also release your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. Non-Personal Information of our Website visitors may also be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses as we see fit in our business. Your information, both Personal Information and Non-Personal Information, may be transferred or shared in the event that the Company undergoes a corporate event, such as a restructuring (including in the event of bankruptcy), merger, divestiture, reorganization, dissolution or other sale of our Company's assets or stock, or other event giving rise to a change of control of our Company.

#### How do we protect your information?

We have implemented measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All Personal Information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls, and any payment transactions will be encrypted. Keep in mind, however, that the safety and security of your information also depends on you; where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect it, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your Personal Information. Any transmission of Personal Information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites, or any information you may provide to such third parties while visiting such third party sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Website and we welcome any feedback about these third party sites that you may wish to share with us. Please email customer-service@gant.com to send us such feedback.

#### Children

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. We do not sell products for purchase by children and all children's products we sell are for purchase by adults only.

#### Your Consent

By using our Website, you consent to the terms of this privacy policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this policy, please do not use the Website.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

California law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. Under the law, a business must either provide this information or permit California residents to opt in to, or opt out of, this type of sharing. We permit California residents to opt out of having their information shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. To opt out, please email customer-service@gant.com.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Website after any such change will constitute your acceptance of the modified terms, so please check periodically for any updates.
